(I regret not meeting you before I married.)
(It's never too late for love.)
(I can't take it anymore.)
(You two, get married right now!)
Jiaojiao, I heard you helped
Youping have a surrogate child. Is that true?
Of course it's true.
If not for that cuckold Song Youhua,
they would have been together long ago.
Song Youhua, I like you.
I'll take care of you from now on.
Song Youhua.
Your test results are out.
It's stomach cancer.
You must have surgery immediately.
Remember to have your family come with you.
Song Youhua.
Why did you go like
Youping's Moments post?
You made him feel guilty.
Don't you know he's in poor health
and can't get emotional?
Jiaojiao.
I need surgery. Can you...
Song Youhua.
Can you stop scheming already?
Your stomach pain
is just a minor problem.
Can it hurt more than Youping's legs?
What would be so bad
if you treated your brother's child
as your own flesh and blood?
I'm doing all this for you.
For me?
All our relatives and friends
treat me like a joke.
You call this for me?
Song Youhua.
I'm carrying the Song family's flesh and blood.
I'm doing this
so that
you brothers won't turn against each other.
But look at you.
You keep throwing
tantrums at me.
If this is what you're like,
how can I
feel secure marrying you?
Perfect.
Then let's not get married.