Song Youhua, I know you too well.
You act stubborn,
but deep down you're afraid I'll break up with you.
You're terrified.
I won't hold it against you this time.
But remember this lesson.
Don't do it again.
Wash my clothes for me.
Then go make a bowl of noodles.
I want to eat when I get back from my shower.
Didn't I tell you to bring a family member?
If something goes wrong in surgery,
there won't even be anyone to sign.
Your brother has an heir now.
Aren't you happy?
Your stomach pain is just a minor problem.
Can it hurt more than Youping's legs?
I'm an orphan.
I have no family.
Happy birthday to you.
Make a wish.
Youhua, why isn't your brother here yet?
Youping, over here.
Youping.
This is your future sister-in-law,
Li Jiaojiao.
Fortunately, the tumor is benign.
You got your life back.
After you go home,
rest well.
Do not get upset.